{
    "id": "c8d17b77127748339e73a7af4c0ddfa7",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………… man in his village.",
            "description": "Eldest is used to speak of people of a family. The superlative form is required here. ",
            "answers": [
                "the eldest",
                "the oldest",
                "the older"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is …………………. botanical garden in the country.",
            "description": "The superlative form is used to compare a person or thing with the whole group they belong to.",
            "answers": [
                "the large",
                "the larger",
                "the largest"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is …………………………. than you think.",
            "description": "Cleverer is the comparative form of clever. ",
            "answers": [
                "more clever",
                "cleverer",
                "more cleverer"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A deer is not as ………………………. as a tiger.",
            "description": "Use the positive form of the adjective in the construction as...as....",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "faster",
                "fastest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She is as …………………………. as you are.",
            "description": "Use the positive form of the adjective in the structure as...as...",
            "answers": [
                "intelligent",
                "more intelligent",
                "intelligenter"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A crow is ……………………….. than a peacock.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "clever",
                "cleverer",
                "cleverest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Platinum is ……………………… than gold.",
            "description": "Costlier is the comparative form of costly.",
            "answers": [
                "costly",
                "costlier",
                "more costly",
                "more costlier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was …………………….. than I thought.",
            "description": "Younger is the comparative form of young.",
            "answers": [
                "young",
                "more young",
                "younger"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron is ………………………. than copper.",
            "description": "More useful is the comparative form of useful",
            "answers": [
                "usefuller",
                "more useful",
                "more usefuller"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron is ………………………….. metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "most useful",
                "the most useful",
                "usefullest",
                "the usefullest"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………. than her sister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "more pretty",
                "prettier",
                "more prettier"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You might think you are ………………………. than him but you aren’t",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "smart",
                "more smart",
                "smarter"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}